$LMU_SliderNudge	<-->
$LMU_HelpMark	(?)
$LMU_Title	Local map
$LMU_Color	Color
$LMU_HelpColor	Renders the local (dungeon/interior) map in color instead of the vanilla black-and-white.
$LMU_FogOfWar	Fog of war
$LMU_HelpFogOfWar	Whether unexplored parts of the local map stay hidden. Disabling reveals the whole map.
$LMU_KeyboardPanSpeed	Keyboard pan speed
$LMU_HelpKeyboardPanSpeed	How fast the local map pans when panning it with the keyboard.
$LMU_ActorMarkers	Actor markers
$LMU_ShowEnemyActors	Show enemy actors
$LMU_ShowHostileActors	Show hostile actors
$LMU_ShowGuardActors	Show guard actors
$LMU_ShowDeadActors	Show dead actors
$LMU_ShowTeammateActors	Show teammate actors
$LMU_ShowNeutralActors	Show neutral actors
$LMU_ImmersiveMode	Immersive mode
$LMU_HelpImmersiveMode	Only shows actor markers on the local map while a detect life/dead effect is active, instead of always. Ships off by default - turn it on if you want markers gated behind a detect effect.
$LMU_MapBorder	Map border
$LMU_HelpMapBorder	Draws a frame around the local map. OFF by default: the game draws its own frame, and most UI replacers draw one too, so this would otherwise stack a second frame on somebody else's. Turn it on if your replacer removed the vanilla frame, or if you prefer ours. Applies live - no need to reopen the map.
$LMU_BorderStyle	Border style
$LMU_HelpBorderStyle	Skyrim: the knotwork frame - the same Nordic art the menu framework's Skyrim theme uses, drawn round the map. The default. Untarnished: a plain single line in Untarnished UI's off-white.
$LMU_Debug	Debug
$LMU_LogLevel	Log level
$LMU_HelpLogLevel	Applies to the log immediately.
$LMU_SaveBtn	Save
$LMU_StatusSaved	Settings saved.
$LMU_StatusSaveFail	Could not save the INI. See the log for why.
$LMU_HelpSave	Writes every setting above back to the INI. Comments and unrelated keys are left alone.
$LMU_ReloadBtn	Reload from INI
$LMU_StatusReloaded	Settings reloaded from the INI.
$LMU_StatusReloadFail	Could not read the INI. See the log for why.
$LMU_HelpReload	Throws away any change made here since the last save and re-reads the INI from disk. Also picks up edits made to the file by hand.
$LMU_RestoreBtn	Restore defaults
$LMU_StatusRestored	Defaults restored. Press Save to keep them.
$LMU_HelpRestore	Puts every setting back to the value it has on a fresh install. Nothing is written until you press Save.
$LMU_Intro	Most settings apply as soon as you make them. Press Save to keep them for the next time you play.
$LMU_LogLevel_Trace	Trace
$LMU_LogLevel_Debug	Debug
$LMU_LogLevel_Info	Info
$LMU_LogLevel_Warning	Warning
$LMU_LogLevel_Error	Error
$LMU_LogLevel_Critical	Critical
$LMU_LogLevel_Off	Off
